<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Code Examples on Practical Process Automation - Book Website</title>
    <link>https://processautomationbook.com/docs/code-examples/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Code Examples on Practical Process Automation - Book Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://processautomationbook.com/docs/code-examples/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Customer Onboarding Example</title>
      <link>https://processautomationbook.com/docs/code-examples/onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://processautomationbook.com/docs/code-examples/onboarding/</guid>
      <description>Customer Onboarding Example #  Alongside Chapter 2, there is this example that shows the customer onboarding process of a fictional telecommunications company as executable process solution.
Link To GitHub #  Customer Onboarding Process on GitHub
Stack #  It used the following stack:
 Camunda Cloud Java Spring Boot  The process model contains three tasks:
 A service task that executes Java Code to score customers A user task so that humans can approve customer orders (or not) A service task that executes glue code to call the REST API of a CRM system  The process solution is a Maven project and contains:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Order Fulfillment Example</title>
      <link>https://processautomationbook.com/docs/code-examples/order-fulfillment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://processautomationbook.com/docs/code-examples/order-fulfillment/</guid>
      <description>Order Fulfillment Microservices Example #  In Chapter 7 and 8, there is this example that shows various microservices interacting to fulfill a customer&amp;rsquo;s order. You can understand that there does not need to be any central orchestration and every microservice might include some process logic. Furthermore, you can also compare the solution approach to a pure event-based choreography.
Link To GitHub #  Order Fulfillment on GitHub
Stack #  It used the following stack:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Examples</title>
      <link>https://processautomationbook.com/docs/code-examples/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://processautomationbook.com/docs/code-examples/other/</guid>
      <description>Other Examples Mentioned in the Book #  Beside the two bigger use cases of Customer Onboarding and Order Fulfillment there are a couple of smaller examples promised in the book. You can find respective links to runnable source example on this page.
Combining Process Models and Programming Code #  As mentioned in Chapter 3 (&amp;ldquo;Combining Process Models and Programming Code&amp;rdquo;), there are three conceptual ways to link BPMN process models with glue code.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
